You can't save the world alone.
Justice League is a action, adventure, science
fiction film directed by Zack Snyder.
Fuelled by his restored faith in humanity and inspired by Superman's selfless act, Bruce Wayne and Diana Prince assemble a team of metahumans consisting of Barry
Allen, Arthur Curry and Victor Stone to face the catastrophic threat of Steppenwolf and the Parademons who are on the hunt for three Mother Boxes on Earth.
Batman / Bruce Wayne, played by Ben Affleck.
Superman / Clark Kent, played by Henry Cavill.
Lois Lane, played by Amy Adams.
Wonder Woman / Diana Prince, played by Gal Gadot.
The Flash / Barry Allen, played by Ezra Miller.
Aquaman / Arthur Curry, played by Jason Momoa.
Justice League is a 2017 American superhero film
based on the DC Comics superhero team.
Produced by Warner Bros.
Pictures, DC Films, RatPac Entertainment, Atlas Entertainment, and
Cruel and Unusual Films, and distributed by Warner Bros.
Pictures, it is the fifth installment in the DC Extended Universe (DCEU).
Directed by Zack Snyder, and written by Chris Terrio and Joss Whedon, the film features an ensemble cast including Ben Affleck, Henry
Cavill, Gal Gadot, Ezra Miller, Jason Momoa, Ray Fisher, Amy Adams, Jeremy Irons, Diane Lane, Connie Nielsen, and J.
In the film, following the events of Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice (2016), Batman and Wonder Woman recruit The Flash, Aquaman, and
Cyborg after the death of Superman to save the world from the catastrophic threat of Steppenwolf and his army of Parademons.
Warner Bros.
began to develop a live-action Justice League film in 2007 with George Miller set to direct,
but the project was canceled due to production delays and budgetary concerns.
Principal photography took place from April to October 2016.
After Snyder stepped down from the film following the death of his daughter, Whedon was hired to oversee the remainder of post-production, including writing and directing
additional scenes, as well as reshooting a large portion of the film, which changed many aspects of it; Snyder ultimately retained sole credit as director.
With an estimated production budget of $300 million, Justice
League is one of the most expensive films ever made.
Justice League premiered at the Dolby Theatre in Hollywood, Los Angeles on November
13, 2017, and was released in the United States four days later.
The film received mixed to negative reviews from critics,  and grossed $661.3
million worldwide against an assumed break-even point of $750 million.
A director's cut, titled Zack Snyder's Justice League, was released on HBO Max in 2021,
following a fan campaign that advocated for Snyder's vision for the film.
The film explores themes of superhero, based on comic, super
power, superhero team, aftercreditsstinger.
The tone is thought_provoking.